{
    "id": "1c6845b170dc4da6bdde4db3279b014f",
    "title": "Rewrite using would rather",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a13d177db8284901bed44019dfbb6d8a",
            "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I would rather you ....................... home now.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go",
                        "went",
                        "had gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would prefer to go in December ..................... in May.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "rather",
                        "rather than",
                        "than"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I prefer starting early rather than ....................... everything to the last minute.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "leave",
                        "to leave",
                        "leaving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I prefer to walk ...................... drive.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "rather",
                        "rather than",
                        "than"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would rather you .................... in a hostel than in a hotel.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "stay",
                        "stayed",
                        "staying"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would rather you ........................ a job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "find",
                        "found",
                        "have found"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ........................ face the enemy than surrender.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "rather",
                        "would rather",
                        "prefer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They would rather build a new house .................... repair the old one.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "than",
                        "then",
                        "than to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We would rather you ......................... to bed now.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go",
                        "went",
                        "have gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We would rather you .................... the work yourself.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "did",
                        "had gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}